TRAIN_DATA = [('tamil nadu bjp vice president explains dmk madhyamuk invite modi party', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE'), (60, 64, 'PERSON'), (11, 14, 'NORP'), (39, 42, 'NORP')]}),
              ('dgp police balachandran passed', {'entities': [(0, 3, 'PERSON'), (11, 23, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('chief minister k palaniswami instructed engage mountaineering training permission forest', {'entities': [(17, 28, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('nel jayaraman suffering cancer saved prayer actor suri', {'entities': [(0, 13, 'PERSON'), (50, 54, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('stalin condemns increasing price petrol diesel price crude oil fallen dollar', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('meteorological department advises fishermen sea', {'entities': [(0, 25, 'ORG')]}),
              ('year old ramanathapuram s church gift king sethupathi beats drum religious harmony', {'entities': [(9, 23, 'GPE'), (43, 53, 'PERSON'), (26, 32, 'LOC')]}),('vijayakanth appeals provide corruption free', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('jayalalithaa sudden campaign chennai supporting aiadmk', {'entities': [(29, 36, 'GPE'), (0, 12, 'PERSON'), (48, 54, 'NORP')]}),('saran son killed', {'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON')]}),('gale blew speed banana trees kumari district plunged darkness second day power cut', {'entities': [(29, 35, 'GPE')]}),('devotees flood tirunallaru kuchanur today shanipairchi', {'entities': [(15, 26, 'GPE'), (27, 35, 'GPE'), (42, 54, 'EVENT')]}),('fisherwomen went sea protested thangachimata demanding release country boat', {'entities': [(31, 44, 'PERSON')]}),('ramadas insists merit test appoint government school special', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'PERSON')]}),('campaigning modi', {'entities': [(12, 16, 'PERSON')]}),('high court adjourned hearing stalin s petition included hearing', {'entities': [(29, 35, 'PERSON'), (0, 10, 'ORG')]}),('chennai govt hospital achieves spinal curvature surgery', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'GPE'), (0, 21, 'ORG')]}),('stalin gattam sing praises jayalalithaa republic', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('arrested assaulting principal pachaiyappan college sent juvenile correctional', {'entities': [(30, 50, 'ORG')]}),('ramadass jobs gave land nlc court', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (24, 33, 'ORG')]}),('jayalalitha afraid mna alliance', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON'), (19, 22, 'NORP')]}),('high court refuses accept vedanta group plea sterlite plant', {'entities': [(26, 39, 'ORG'), (45, 53, 'PRODUCT')]}),('brinda s question case registered police opened fire', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('publication poetry book maha periyava written poet', {'entities': [(24, 37, 'PERSON')]}),('dmk leader vijayakanth accused dmk aiadmk governments prolonging jallikattu', {'entities': [(11, 22, 'PERSON'), (0, 3, 'NORP'), (31, 34, 'NORP'), (35, 41, 'NORP'), (65, 75, 'EVENT')]}),('jeyakumar said ops s idea ​​an early election tamil nadu', {'entities': [(46, 56, 'GPE'), (0, 9, 'PERSON'), (15, 18, 'PERSON')]}),('demudika mlas explain legislative assembly', {'entities': [(22, 42, 'ORG')]}),('rahul gandhi apologizes canceling campaign tamil', {'entities': [(0, 12, 'PERSON'), (43, 48, 'LANGUAGE')]}),('swine flu challenge health officials affected people tamil nadu claimed', {'entities': [(53, 63, 'GPE')]}),('vallalar memorial day feb st holiday tasmac', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (37, 43, 'ORG')]}),('sslc public exam answer sheet evaluation starts', {'entities': [(0, 4, 'ORG')]}),('ready pay price save dtv dhinakaran sampath interview', {'entities': [(25, 35, 'PERSON'), (36, 43, 'PERSON')]}),('farmers comrade turned businessman manuneethi manickam atappa', {'entities': [(35, 61, 'PERSON')]}),('ramadas condemns thug law amendment death knell', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'PERSON')]}),('srirangam election dmk candidate filing', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'GPE'), (19, 22, 'ORG')]}),('person arrested kodanad estate murder', {'entities': [(16, 30, 'FAC')]}),('car award winning driver interviews tamed bulls round alankanallur', {'entities': [(54, 66, 'GPE')]}),('north east monsoon likely start puducherry tamil nadu', {'entities': [(43, 53, 'GPE'), (0, 10, 'LOC')]}),('members general assembly supported dhinakaran puduvai thanga tamilchelvan', {'entities': [(35, 45, 'PERSON'), (54, 73, 'PERSON'), (8, 24, 'ORG')]}),('dmk president karunanidhi condoles death martyr mayanti', {'entities': [(14, 25, 'PERSON'), (48, 55, 'PERSON'), (0, 3, 'FAC')]}),('fortis malar hospital doctors advise treatment quickly heart attack occurs death', {'entities': [(0, 21, 'FAC')]}),('madhyamik general secretary vaiko accused modi amit shah s support h raja s outrageous', {'entities': [(28, 33, 'PERSON'), (42, 46, 'PERSON'), (47, 56, 'PERSON'), (67, 73, 'PERSON')]}),('tirupur knitwear workers paid old currency', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'GPE')]}),('sugarcane farmers protest chennai', {'entities': [(26, 33, 'GPE'), (0, 9, 'PRODUCT')]}),('police nets dmk volunteer worker barged biryani shop virugambakkam punched manager boxing style', {'entities': [(53, 66, 'GPE'), (12, 15, 'NORP'), (40, 47, 'PRODUCT')]}),('namitha argue election officials husband', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'PERSON')]}),('high court bans myshkin directing crime', {'entities': [(16, 23, 'PERSON')]}),('aiadmk team plans meet camp election commission officials', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'NORP'), (28, 47, 'ORG')]}),('stalin s drama cauvery issue reviewed minister', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('chennai student raika jaman topped', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'GPE'), (16, 27, 'PERSON')]}),('sri lanka refugee camp student denied medical', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'GPE'), (10, 22, 'FAC')]}),('aiadmk councilor urges removal tasmac bar', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'NORP')]}),('chief minister explained student varamathi arrested goonter', {'entities': [(33, 42, 'PERSON')]}),('jayalalithaa verdict echoes effigies paraded', {'entities': [(0, 12, 'PERSON')]}),('apply govt computer certificate', {'entities': [(6, 10, 'ORG')]}),('hour long interrogation ram mohana rao s friend lawyer', {'entities': [(28, 38, 'PERSON')]}),('background madurai aap leader manisai ops brother raja s sudden dismissal aiadmk responsibilities including membership party', {'entities': [(11, 18, 'GPE'), (30, 41, 'PERSON'), (50, 54, 'PERSON'), (19, 22, 'NORP'), (74, 80, 'NORP')]}),('declaration tawheed jama', {'entities': [(12, 24, 'PERSON')]}),('tamilisai sterlite plant s seven stopped interview buy tomorrow brother angry release', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (10, 24, 'ORG')]}),('kerala consumer court orders compensation rs tamil nadu devotee forcibly evicted hostel elderly', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'GPE'), (45, 55, 'GPE')]}),('karunanidhi contesting tiruvarur', {'entities': [(23, 32, 'GPE'), (0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('ops explains bus fares decreased despite lower diesel', {'entities': [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]}),('pr pandian demands removal sadananda gowda union', {'entities': [(27, 48, 'GPE'), (0, 10, 'PERSON')]}),('persons wanted kolathur jewelery shop', {'entities': [(15, 32, 'ORG')]}),('cross examination mq stalin case kolathur constituency', {'entities': [(33, 41, 'GPE'), (21, 27, 'PERSON')]}),('aamuk announced candidate srirangam', {'entities': [(26, 35, 'GPE')]}),('stalin declare tamil nadu drought state provide relief', {'entities': [(15, 25, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('evergreen memories karunanidhi s pet paridhi youngavaluti surrendered jayalalithaa person fought legislative', {'entities': [(19, 30, 'PERSON'), (70, 82, 'PERSON')]}),('movement coordinator thirumurugan gandhi arrested', {'entities': [(21, 40, 'PERSON')]}),('democratic party india sowing seeds success conducting free medical', {'entities': [(17, 22, 'GPE'), (0, 16, 'ORG')]}),('sasikala saw jayalalithaa apollo ops', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (13, 25, 'PERSON'), (26, 32, 'ORG')]}),('ms swaminathan s young generation farm new technology adapt climate', {'entities': [(3, 14, 'PERSON')]}),('human rights commission notice tamil nadu government report maulivakkam building accident', {'entities': [(31, 41, 'GPE'), (60, 71, 'GPE'), (0, 23, 'ORG')]}),('person donated blood pray chief minister jayalalithaa s speedy recovery following physiotherapy', {'entities': [(41, 53, 'PERSON')]}),('union minister narayanasamy accused tamil nadu government delaying talks fishermen', {'entities': [(36, 46, 'GPE'), (15, 27, 'PERSON')]}),('new administrators tamil nadu congress fishermen', {'entities': [(19, 29, 'GPE'), (30, 38, 'NORP')]}),('anticipatory bail srirangam bjp', {'entities': [(18, 27, 'GPE'), (28, 31, 'NORP')]}),('bar council order lifting ban suspended', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'ORG')]}),('lok adalat lakh cases settlement tamil nadu state legal affairs commission secretary', {'entities': [(33, 43, 'GPE'), (44, 74, 'ORG'), (0, 21, 'EVENT')]}),('tens thousands devotees thronged mylapore kapaleeswarar temple maha kumbabhishekam', {'entities': [(33, 41, 'GPE'), (33, 62, 'LOC'), (63, 82, 'EVENT')]}),('actor sivakumar urukkam enforce alcohol prohibition matter', {'entities': [(6, 23, 'PERSON')]}),('lakhs thronged rto offices days following original driving license', {'entities': [(15, 18, 'ORG')]}),('humanity people s party supports dmk s', {'entities': [(33, 36, 'NORP')]}),('cauvery management board confirmed tamilisai', {'entities': [(35, 44, 'PERSON'), (0, 7, 'LOC')]}),('chennai bus station mothers benefit lactation', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'GPE')]}),('thirumavalavan needs judicial investigation kurangani fire', {'entities': [(44, 53, 'GPE'), (0, 14, 'PERSON')]}),('chief minister inaugurate world investors conference', {'entities': [(26, 52, 'EVENT')]}),('jayalalitha s meeting actors union disappointment', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('deal north east monsoon rains police officials advise measures prevent cell phone', {'entities': [(5, 15, 'LOC')]}),('income tax audit vijayabaskar s father', {'entities': [(17, 29, 'PERSON')]}),('doesn t matter domestically abroad bring corrupt justice pm modi assured madurai bjp', {'entities': [(73, 80, 'GPE'), (60, 64, 'PERSON'), (81, 84, 'NORP')]}),('final phase production sivakasi busy sending firecrackers outlying', {'entities': [(23, 31, 'GPE')]}),('training minister ka sengottaiyan informs school students enroll accounts auditor', {'entities': [(18, 33, 'PERSON')]}),('computerized fir clerk computer operator training april police stations tamil', {'entities': [(72, 77, 'LANGUAGE')]}),('sonia rahul boycott sivaganga displeasure chidambaram', {'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON'), (6, 11, 'PERSON'), (42, 53, 'PERSON')]}),('massive blood donation camp held shirdi dec sri saibaba', {'entities': [(33, 39, 'GPE')]}),('aiadmk win way contest vasudevanallur constituency', {'entities': [(23, 37, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'NORP')]}),('car overturned near vedasandur killing including', {'entities': [(20, 30, 'GPE')]}),('background cancellation election aravakurichi thanjavur rs crore', {'entities': [(46, 55, 'GPE')]}),('vijayakanth condemned chief minister sand mining completely stopped', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('decision communist party india election results discussed executive committee', {'entities': [(25, 30, 'GPE'), (9, 24, 'NORP')]}),('dependent sasikala dhinakaran minister jayakumar', {'entities': [(10, 18, 'PERSON'), (19, 29, 'PERSON'), (39, 48, 'PERSON')]}),('vyasarpadi prepares watch world cup football final wide', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE'), (26, 35, 'EVENT')]}),('govt s smart card scheme ready eliminate fake ration cards priority given ariyalur perambalur leader aadhaar enrolment', {'entities': [(83, 93, 'GPE')]}),('campaign supporting dmk candidate tiruvarur constituency election dmk general secretary vaiko', {'entities': [(34, 43, 'GPE'), (88, 93, 'PERSON')]}),('chief minister jayalalithaa orders quick action rape girls', {'entities': [(15, 27, 'PERSON')]}),('protest land acquisition nlc company people including women set fire officers attacked arresting', {'entities': [(25, 28, 'ORG')]}),('thirumavalavan interview krishnagiri provide free education research', {'entities': [(25, 36, 'GPE'), (0, 14, 'PERSON')]}),('chief minister vinayagar chaturthi wish success', {'entities': [(15, 34, 'EVENT')]}),('sudden u turn rk nagar election double leaf symbol', {'entities': [(14, 22, 'GPE')]}),('thousands devotees took holy dip tiruchanur panchami theertha festival', {'entities': [(33, 70, 'EVENT')]}),('abhinandan s father urukkam wants son', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'PERSON')]}),('anbumani ramadoss letter modi exempt tamil nadu neet', {'entities': [(0, 17, 'PERSON')]}),('neutrino project controversial communist party state', {'entities': [(31, 46, 'NORP')]}),('election commission maneka gandhi s speech khushbu', {'entities': [(20, 33, 'PERSON'), (43, 50, 'PERSON'), (0, 19, 'ORG')]}),('ramadoss asked india condemns america bows sri', {'entities': [(15, 20, 'GPE'), (30, 37, 'GPE'), (0, 8, 'PERSON')]}),('anbumani alleged dharmapuri achievement tamil nadu government sale', {'entities': [(17, 27, 'GPE'), (40, 50, 'GPE'), (0, 8, 'PERSON')]}),('transfer sps tamil', {'entities': [(13, 18, 'LANGUAGE')]}),('tiruvallur district police arrested man found banned tobacco products worth', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE')]}),('government s indifference farmers puducherry district demanded remove', {'entities': [(34, 44, 'GPE')]}),('election officer tamil nadu appealed vacant', {'entities': [(17, 27, 'GPE')]}),('sand robbery vaigai river ruining tamil nadu s water source construction', {'entities': [(34, 44, 'GPE'), (13, 25, 'LOC')]}),('malpractice agricultural university vice chancellor s exam form new search committee', {'entities': [(12, 35, 'ORG')]}),('puducherry governor kiranbedi orders collect details politicians associated', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE'), (20, 29, 'PERSON')]}),('manonmaniam sundaranar university corruption vice chancellor ramadoss', {'entities': [(61, 69, 'PERSON'), (0, 33, 'ORG')]}),('dmk election campaign', {'entities': [(0, 3, 'NORP')]}),('minute traffic stop chennai occasion martyrs', {'entities': [(20, 27, 'GPE')]}),('change decision dependent dhinakaran', {'entities': [(26, 36, 'PERSON')]}),('jayakumar dmk conference pass resolution karnataka congress government cauvery', {'entities': [(41, 50, 'GPE'), (0, 9, 'PERSON'), (10, 13, 'NORP'), (51, 59, 'NORP')]}),('lawyer arrested madurai', {'entities': [(16, 23, 'GPE')]}),('chief minister k palaniswami s announcement raise lawyers provident fund', {'entities': [(15, 28, 'PERSON')]}),('amit shah participate branch committee meeting held volunteer house', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'PERSON')]}),('aiadmk officials disappointed invitation interviews nellai district', {'entities': [(52, 58, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'NORP')]}),('freshwater turtles tried smuggled sri lanka seized arrested', {'entities': [(34, 43, 'GPE')]}),('dinakaran s pro mps join forces meet edappadi', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (37, 45, 'PERSON')]}),('mdmk high level committee meeting', {'entities': [(0, 4, 'ORG')]}),('madurai municipal corporation announces rs lakh prize clean residence eradicate', {'entities': [(0, 29, 'ORG')]}),('fire private warehouse chennai caused damage goods worth crores', {'entities': [(23, 30, 'GPE')]}),('vaigo urges india participate sri lankan military', {'entities': [(12, 17, 'GPE'), (0, 5, 'PERSON')]}),('stalin s explanation insisting convening tamil nadu legislative', {'entities': [(41, 51, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('gst raid vishal s house vigo condemns central govt s', {'entities': [(9, 15, 'GPE')]}),('tarun vijay mp insists erecting valluvar statue state', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON'), (32, 40, 'PERSON')]}),('karunanidhi appeals dmk huge funds face election', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON'), (20, 23, 'NORP')]}),('tamil nadu ips officers undergoing drastic', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE')]}),('kolathur star block stalin s', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'GPE')]}),('chennai corporation s plan set vocational training centers informed mayor saidai', {'entities': [(74, 80, 'PERSON'), (0, 19, 'ORG')]}),('according health minister vijayabaskar tamil nadu government decide score wrote neet exam tamil based cbse', {'entities': [(39, 49, 'GPE'), (26, 38, 'PERSON'), (39, 44, 'LANGUAGE'), (90, 95, 'LANGUAGE')]}),('jallikattu dmk aiadmk betrayed ramdas', {'entities': [(31, 37, 'PERSON'), (11, 14, 'NORP'), (0, 10, 'EVENT')]}),('project report soil test land survey completed aiims hospital foundation soon madurai minister vijayabaskar', {'entities': [(78, 85, 'GPE'), (95, 107, 'PERSON'), (47, 72, 'ORG')]}),('forest college students request sarathkumar appeal chief', {'entities': [(32, 43, 'PERSON')]}),('class boycott esi medical college students fast th', {'entities': [(14, 17, 'ORG')]}),('adhambakkam lake shrunk hectare hectare', {'entities': [(0, 16, 'LOC')]}),('plant management explained sterlite plant shut days maintenance', {'entities': [(27, 41, 'FAC')]}),('ready battle leader dharma fans calling rajini', {'entities': [(20, 26, 'PERSON'), (40, 46, 'PERSON')]}),('research student s bail plea dismissed nirmala devi', {'entities': [(39, 51, 'PERSON')]}),('revenue minister rb udayakumar information precautionary measures avoid loss life damage northeast', {'entities': [(20, 30, 'PERSON')]}),('according gk vasan tamil nadu s kurvai cultivation achieved getting water', {'entities': [(19, 29, 'GPE'), (10, 18, 'PERSON')]}),('chennai egmore court summons chidambaram family case concealment foreign assets appear', {'entities': [(0, 14, 'GPE'), (29, 40, 'PERSON')]}),('people gathered pay respects manthivela doctor passed away provided treatment fee', {'entities': [(29, 39, 'PERSON')]}),('district collector ordered respond suit seeking monitoring toilet facilities government government aided schools kanchipuram', {'entities': [(113, 124, 'GPE')]}),('today world anesthesiology day need raise awareness vital role anesthesiologists', {'entities': [(6, 30, 'EVENT')]}),('high court today heard appeal judge session seeking ban jakto jio', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'ORG')]}),('duraimurugan expected ascend throne leader dmk stalin s', {'entities': [(0, 12, 'PERSON'), (47, 53, 'PERSON')]}),('tamil nadu cabinet meeting today discuss assembly', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE'), (41, 49, 'ORG')]}),('don t need support proxy ministers manoj pandian', {'entities': [(35, 48, 'PERSON')]}),('chief minister k palaniswami plans stop eggs nutrition', {'entities': [(15, 28, 'PERSON')]}),('ramadoss withdraw order demanding increase revenue autonomous', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON')]}),('chennai salem road project ordinance cancels land acquisition high court action', {'entities': [(0, 7, 'GPE'), (8, 13, 'GPE')]}),('rajinikanth meets', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('aiims hospital tamil nadu decided central government tamilnadu health secretary informs', {'entities': [(15, 25, 'GPE')]}),('ramadoss accused higher education department canceling appointment vice chancellor madurai kamaraj university', {'entities': [(83, 90, 'GPE'), (0, 8, 'PERSON'), (17, 44, 'ORG'), (91, 109, 'ORG')]}),('seeman accused waive farm loans', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('prime minister narendra modi participate consecration tall statue adiyogi shiva isha yoga', {'entities': [(24, 28, 'PERSON')]}),('karunanidhi s letter asking support dmk general', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),('tamil nadu chief minister approves construction new houses demolishing', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'GPE')]}),('rahul soon visit tamil nadu day tour thirunavukkarasar', {'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON')]}),('aiadmk wins karunanidhi paying', {'entities': [(12, 23, 'PERSON'), (0, 6, 'NORP')]}),('contested delhi despite threats', {'entities': [(10, 15, 'GPE')]}),('advani rahul s visit today leaders tamil nadu', {'entities': [(35, 45, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'PERSON'), (7, 12, 'PERSON')]}),('demonstration chennai kerala government hope finding good solution sabarimala', {'entities': [(14, 21, 'GPE'), (22, 28, 'GPE'), (67, 77, 'GPE')]}),('dec legal defense conference thirumavalavan', {'entities': [(29, 43, 'PERSON')]}),('ramdas planned violence', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),('hope minister sellur raju come', {'entities': [(14, 25, 'PERSON')]}),('sri lankan government recommended release fishermen refused release', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'NORP')]}),('government polytechnic students admitted coimbatore hospital food', {'entities': [(41, 51, 'GPE'), (41, 60, 'FAC')]}),('elections like festival political parties interested campaigning rk nagar constituency', {'entities': [(65, 73, 'GPE')]}),('heavy rain likely north tamil nadu chennai meteorological', {'entities': [(24, 34, 'GPE'), (35, 42, 'GPE')]}),('rk nagar election polling', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'GPE')]}),('chennai corporation s run crematoriums gas prevent high electricity costs air pollution easy maintain smoke', {'entities': [(0, 19, 'ORG')]}),
              ('mutharasan wishes karunanidhi speedy', {'entities': [(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (18, 29, 'PERSON')]}),('stalin s interview budget speech', {'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('nellalai hindu girl today women s festival global law needed prevent cybercrime manonmaniam sundaranar university professor', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'GPE'), (9, 14, 'NORP')]}),
              ('computer center run women damaged floods nellai goods worth rs', {'entities': [(41, 47, 'GPE')]}),
              ('kanyakumari district admk camp votes minority people dmk congress', {'entities': [(21, 25, 'NORP'), (53, 56, 'NORP'), (57, 65, 'NORP')]}),
              ('minister velumani launched work making geospatial map chennai corporation unmanned aerial', {'entities': [(9, 17, 'PERSON'), (54, 73, 'ORG')]}),
              ('ramdas chatal says aiadmk s factions joining forces', {'entities': [(0, 13, 'PERSON'), (19, 25, 'ORG')]}),
              ('marxist communist party announced public meeting movement tamil nadu condemn central state', {'entities': [(58, 68, 'GPE'), (0, 7, 'NORP'), (8, 23, 'NORP')]}),
              ('sarathkumar s meeting chief minister palaniswami urges protect firecrackers', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON'), (37, 48, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('engineering student mysterious death pollachi branch jail jail superintendent', {'entities': [(37, 45, 'GPE')]}),
              ('arrangements send swiss woman lost memories chennai home country intensive', {'entities': [(44, 51, 'GPE'), (18, 23, 'NORP')]}),
              ('vijayakanth wish dmk contest', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('land right way road affected people august salem marxist', {'entities': [(43, 48, 'GPE')]}),
              ('udumalaipet police station torture woman police responded high', {'entities': [(0, 11, 'GPE')]}),
              ('senior members feel confusion caused change aiadmk s administrative boundaries setback minister sewur', {'entities': [(96, 101, 'GPE'), (44, 50, 'NORP')]}),
              ('g ramakrishnan announces marxist contesting local body', {'entities': [(0, 14, 'PERSON'), (25, 32, 'NORP')]}),
              ('chief minister jayalalithaa launched vehicle service air pollution measuring facility cost', {'entities': [(15, 27, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('rajnivas know truth people s attempt besiege kiranbedi went', {'entities': [(45, 54, 'GPE'), (0, 8, 'FAC')]}),
              ('high court ordered tamil nadu government consider case seeking provide flood relief heads', {'entities': [(19, 29, 'GPE')]}),
              ('minister jayakumar informed people want tiruvarur elections fully recovered effects cyclone', {'entities': [(40, 49, 'GPE'), (9, 18, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('ramadoss remove temporary teachers anna', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (35, 39, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('chief minister jayalalithaa s speech action commits mistake', {'entities': [(15, 27, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('jayalalithaa changed candidates overcome bjp crisis nagercoil vedaranyam', {'entities': [(52, 61, 'GPE'), (0, 12, 'PERSON'), (41, 44, 'NORP')]}),
              ('mam ramaswami chettiar multi faceted', {'entities': [(4, 22, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('ramadoss insists controlling fast spreading swine', {'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('aiadmk active dindigul', {'entities': [(14, 22, 'GPE'), (0, 6, 'NORP')]}),
              ('february tamil nadu s lawyers decided boycott court', {'entities': [(9, 19, 'GPE')]}),
              ('vasan says central government treacherous cauvery', {'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON'), (11, 29, 'ORG'), (42, 49, 'LOC')]}),
              ('lack monitoring plastic usage kumari increasing piling', {'entities': [(30, 36, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('dmk members continue act action council president', {'entities': [(0, 3, 'NORP')]}),
              ('tnpsc notification certificate verification nav executive officer', {'entities': [(0, 5, 'ORG')]}),
              ('raghuram rajan committee recommendations implemented cm s letter', {'entities': [(0, 14, 'PERSON')]}),
              ('srirangam election bjp candidate filing', {'entities': [(0, 9, 'GPE'), (19, 22, 'NORP')]}),
              ('year treatment karunanidhi came murasoli s office visited murasoli coral festival stage dmk members happy', {'entities': [(15, 26, 'PERSON')]})]